I'm going to share my screen.
There we go. Are you able to see?
Yes.
Right.
Let's do, let's say, this one, so one.
And then after you see this,
if you could like, you know,
basically kind of identify what we need
to add, what we need to get rid of,
and what you actually put into that
screen,
and then we can take it from there.
So...
Okay.
Can we back up just a bit?
I want to understand your workflow here.
Yeah.
And so I think I saw that you were
connected to a knowledge base.
Actually,
that knowledge base step is right now,
it's disabled until we figure out how to
utilize knowledge bases better in the
workflow.
Because of current design of how the
knowledge base works in Vanalyzer,
it can't quite do the job.
So currently that step is kind of
disabled.
But in the future,
once we do get knowledge bases working,
you can kind of give input into what
knowledge base we could use and like what
would be useful in this case.
Yeah.
So, I think...
Knowledge bases could be.
useful in this workflow.
If it could work the way that I would
like it to work.
Yeah.
What I mean by that is,
there isn't necessarily...
one specific knowledge base to use for
all export to banners because our
Mhm.
sponsors are all different and
Yeah.
What you would really want to point to is
the sponsor's general terms and
conditions. So like this,
I notice you're using an NSF award.
And so we would, yeah,
we would want it to point to the PPAPPG.
Should be the PAPPG.
But if it was NIH,
we'd want it to point to the NIH terms
and conditions. If it was USDA.
Yeah, you know, so on and so forth.
Yeah.
So is there a way to utilize a workflow?
but then ask it to point to a different
knowledge base each time.
Or do you just select the knowledge base
and the award letter when you run the
workflow?
So there's two ways we could tackle this.
First,
what you said is have it like in the
disclaimer of the workflow that before
you run the workflow,
you go into that knowledge base step and
select the knowledge base based on which
agency the document is from.
Or if this is,
we could also have like just different
variations of the workflow, like,
you know,
export the banner in parentheses, NIH,
NSF, and all that,
if we want to save Dari's time of like,
you know.
Okay,
so that would be very simple if we just,
you know,
it would be just like basically the same
copy of the workflow,
but like the knowledge base pre-selected
based on the different agency variations.
Yeah, I like that. Okay. Okay, so that's,
I guess, my first comment.
Awesome.
And then it looks like the rest of the
workflow was built utilizing extraction.
Is that right?
Yeah, well,
like an extraction task or like I did use
prompt tasks,
but in this case it works as an
extraction task.
Uh-huh.
Okay,
and you probably are extracting
information that I described in the video,
right?
Yeah.
Got it.
Okay.
And this was specifically, uh,
it's worth the banner, the form review.
What?
Yeah, yeah, OK.
Um...
I think what would work best?
Yes, if.
I could take some time to match up.
what it's giving you against the export
to Banner form and see what I left out of
my video.
Because I have no doubt that you probably
Awesome, yeah.
did exactly as my video stated.
And yeah, it's yeah.
What did I miss when I did when I did the
video?
It has been a while. And see,
I was thinking about this yesterday, like,
gosh, before we meet,
should I send you a copy of the output?
And then Barrie and I got like, you know,
too deep into the rabbit hole with our
evaluation stuff,
and that just kind of slipped my mind.
But I will e-mail you like that copy of
that output right now,
so that later you can take your time.
Okay.
And, like, you know, match it up.
I have,
I need to do an export to banner review
today. So this will be,
this will be a good,
Oh, awesome.
it'll be easy for me to.
to evaluate this and let you know what I
missed.
I'm wondering, so...
You tell me. I created a while ago.
Who?
A workflow for myself of two.
Problematic.
areas that I have during the review.
the two areas that are difficult for me
to find the information in the award
Mhm.
document.
And so I created a workflow that I call
E2B reviews.
And.
To help me pull out.
It's mostly reporting requirements and
billing requirements.
So you tell me in your workflow,
does it have billing requirements and
reporting requirements?
Should let me just double check.
It's got special terms and F. Okay,
that's near the. Yes,
reporting compliance, billing and payment.
I think you mentioned that in the, like,
hold on,
Okay, good.
let me share it in to just kind of show
you.
So yeah,
it's got like a dedicated section for
billing and payment and then reporting
and compliance if it's mentioned in the
award.
OK.
Okay.
Great.
Um...
One thing when we do pull in.
Um...
A knowledge base.
Yeah.
that will want to ensure that the
workflow has instructions for is if there
are
Differing information between...
The Award.
versus the terms and conditions.
We want the terms and conditions to take,
Mhm.
or excuse me,
we want the award to take precedent.
Okay.
So that would want, you know,
when we do build that,
we would want that to be explicit in
there.
Okay.
Yeah.
Um, what else can I think of right now?
Yeah, I think I just want to.
try it out and let you know maybe things
that I missed.
Mhm.
Yeah,
I think the other thing that I might run
Yeah.
into is...
Some of these values are simply pulling
out.
you know, some words out of the award,
but some of it is...
Making decisions.
Mhm.
I show you something and then maybe it'll.
It will describe it better.
The.
Take me a minute to get my screens where
they need to be, and then I'll share.
No problem.
Yeah.
I just tie up.
I'm not, I get frustrated with Veris.
It's a good thing it's going away then.
Just like the amount of clicks to get to
something is.
Alright, crazy.
Export.
Theater.
Okay, sure.
Let's see,
I think there's one on the first page.
Here's a good example.
Are you able to see my screen? Okay. 1.12.
Yeah.
This drop-down menu here,
the award document might actually mention
these words.
And what I have found is some sponsors
Mmh.
incorrectly identify the document as,
for example,
they might call the document in the award
document a contract,
but then when we read through it,
we realize, no, actually,
Yeah.
it's a grant or actually it's a
cooperative agreement.
And so the way we've dealt with this and
Barrie is to help our
analysts are these help tips over to the
side.
So this is what they need to think about
before they click on one of those.
Yeah.
Regardless of what the Award document
actually says.
This is how they need to make that
determination.
Okay.
And so my guess is in the workflow,
it may pull out.
one of these terms,
but don't you think it's probably basing
it on...
the words in the document as opposed to
the attributes that the project actually
is.
Yeah.
So I'm wondering how we can build this
kind of decision making into a workflow,
or maybe it's not possible.
Well,
it is kind of possible because of
depending on how we design the prompt,
in the prompt we would tell it to make
those decisions based on the wording
rather than what's just, you know,
subtly or like just mentioned in the
document itself.
So it is definitely possible if we make
the prompt have that decision step.
Yeah.
and add, you know,
that critical thinking part of it.
This is another example,
like this award category.
You can see there's lots of different
choices here. And again,
we created a document to help the analyst
decide what to select here.
Mhm.
So we have a lot of this throughout the
export to Banner form,
a lot of these guides on how to make the
correct selection.
So I'll take a look at what that output
was. And like I said, I have this.
I actually have one,
this one that I need to review today,
Mhm.
so I can compare it and then give you
some feedback.
Okay, awesome.
Trying to think if there's anything else
that I had thought of.
Ohh,
let me show you once one place in the
export to banner form that.
I think we could also build into a
workflow. We call this FOI text.
This is just the banner form where this
information lives. And as you can see,
there's a lot of information here.
And the way that this works is we have
some standard
Terms that we see quite often in awards,
and if the analyst...
Yeah.
in reviewing the award, discovers that,
for example, we need this,
then they'll just make a selection over
here.
And that will then when this exports.
that term will show up in the FOIA text
banner form.
So not all of these will show up.
Only the ones that are checked are on the
far left. So as you can see,
Wes is the one that did this one and he
Okay.
added these two.
Terms,
and but all the others won't show up.
Mhm.
As you can imagine,
this area takes quite a bit of time for
the analyst.
To find all of the to see if any of these
exist in a document.
And I would love to see in the workflow.
it actually doing the work for us as much
as possible.
Yeah.
Do you think that's something that we
could build in?
Oh, yes, especially like, you know,
these terms, like,
we could definitely make a workflow that,
you know,
kind of flags it or like the part of this
workflow and add like a different contest
that its explicit task is to do this,
like, you know,
take all these terms and see if they're
mentioned at.
Any point in the document, and if so,
in the output we would add in another
section, the foil line text, let's say,
and then it would list like, "Hey,
this is here in the document where this
was mentioned,
" and then that would make the RS job
easier instead of going through all of
these and...
There's quite a lot.
I see the toolbar on the right.
Yes, look at that. I mean,
it's kind of crazy.
I was like, wow.
And when I first started being the
reviewer...
Mhm.
I was just like, oh my gosh. I mean,
this is where I spent most of my time
trying to figure it out.
Yeah. And are these terms or like,
I guess, phrases,
do you guys always update them or are at
least is there like a general like,
you know,
bank of terms like this that are like
commonly that you guys flag for?
Yeah,
these are the common ones that we're
looking for.
Then what you'll see, like for instance,
this one on sequence 202,
Yeah.
I probably said something like point of
contact.
Yeah.
And then what Wes did is he flagged that
and then added in from the award who the
actual point of contact is.
But the boilerplate.
would have just said, you know,
point of contact.
I was trying to up here,
a lot of times I'll see.
Like, you'll see this one.
So we have some that are pretty,
Yeah.
that we see quite often,
but then there could be other
restrictions than the award.
And if there were, you would mark this,
but you'd probably, you know,
do something like no publication.
Yeah.
Post allowed, right? And so...
It's mostly there,
but then we'll tailor it to the very
specific award, if that makes sense.
OK, then.
Yeah, and later on when you have a chance,
could you send me like, like, you know,
like a PDF version of this page or just
even like the list of terms so I can
Hi.
start to bake it into the workflow?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Where's another one?
Oh, this one doesn't have it,
but a lot of times maybe like final
billing, this is pretty standard, like 30,
45, or 60 days.
Mhm.
But there might actually be a date in the
award, like final is due on December 10th,
2029 or something like that. So again,
we'd flag it and then we would,
Yes.
we might add some.
The specifics.
Okay.
Yeah.
Like this is very specific to the award
and I am not sure exactly what would have
been there.
But okay, yeah,
this is this is the challenge.
for sure.
And this is where I think we probably
The.
miss some because it is so labor
intensive and we have a human doing it.
Yeah.
So being able to have a machine and a
human do it.
Yeah.
People will get better at it, K.
Mhm.
I think those are the things I wanted to
chat with you about.
Awesome.
Yeah. Okay.
How are the rest of your meetings going
with RAs?
Good. With RAs. So remember,
Emily was the only person that was left
to go over like the process mapping stuff.
And we finally set up like a meeting
because she was like busy and then it was
supposed to be this week,
but then Sammy's out. So we're meeting
the following Friday.
So after that is wrapped,
we have all the process maps basically
done. And then as far as meetings,
the one with Cindy went well.
Barrie and I are working on it. And then..
.
Today, at 11,
we have what I'm excited for,
a meeting with Tammy to combine the RFA
and FOA checklist into one.
And which is also awesome because the
evaluation me and Barrie are working on,
like even for like vandalizer accuracy
metrics, as well as like, you know.
making like a whole like benchmark or
data set of how to evaluate workflows,
the timeline matched up pretty nicely
because we're at a point in that
evaluation, we're thinking, all right,
what should we get rid of in this
workflow?
And so that's the one I'm excited for
today.
Oh, good.
And she will be very critical and provide
a lot of feedback, which is good,
which is very good. And she has,
Yes, exactly.
I know she has created other workflows.
And so she.
might have ideas on how to incorporate
some other things.
Things into that into your workflow that
you're creating for her,
but she's she's one of our active
vandalizer users,
Yeah, yeah.
so I think she'll she'll provide a lot of
really good feedback.
I know,
that's what I noticed in like Barry and I
were talking that you guys also had this
conversation. It's hard to,
I feel like in meetings,
not always people are like, you know,
fully, you know,
feel comfortable to give feedback or
critical, but with Tammy,
I've noticed it's so helpful. Like she,
Yeah.
even the smallest details,
He will tell you.
Which is exactly what we want, you know?
Yeah.
She will tell you she has no qualms of
giving feedback. Yeah, yeah.
No, and that is perfect for, like,
you know, developing workflows and all.
All this year.
Yeah,
because we want to also get to a point
where they are using these workflows,
you know, so yeah,
Exactly.
I'm excited for that one because I know.
I know she'll give the feedback.
And so it may take a few times going back
and forth with her to get it to where she
likes it.
Yeah.
But if we can get her buy-in on that
workflow,
she'll convince the rest of the
preawarduidahoedu team to start using it.
And that's of course what we want.
We want them to start using these
Yeah.
workflows.
Yeah, okay, good. I'm glad.
And Barry's so good at bridging that gap
between developer and RA. You know,
I think adding him to those meetings will
Uh-huh.
be helpful for both sides.
Alright,
is there anything else you need from me?
I know this is helpful.
I've been given my assignment and I will
give you,
get you feedback once I have a chance to
dig into it, okay?
Yeah.
Awesome. Well,
see you at 3:30 for our DGA meeting.
Yes, yeah,
we'll check in with them and think I'm
Yeah.
going to need to prod them a little bit
more because we have not received any new
Okay, yeah.
project ideas. So.
That's okay.
We've got plenty of other things to work
Yeah.
on. But it's like,
if you want us to help you,
you have to give us your ideas. So, yeah.
Okay. All right. Talk to you later.
Yeah.
Hello, Michele.
Thanks, Labib.
Yeah, thank you. Bye.
Okay, bye.